



Ageel Ur Rehman Chishti

Nationality: Pakistani Date of birth: 20/05/1996

Phone number: (+92) 3142881710 Email address: ageel.chishti@outlook.com

○ Whatsapp Messenger: +923142881710

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ageelchishti/

Website: https://ageelchishti.github.io/

• Home: Goth Ghani, Near Railway Station, P/O Khas, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

ABOUT ME

I'm an experienced SvelteKit Frontend Developer having 3+ years of experience in Svelte / SvelteKit with SSR, Tailwind CSS, Typescript & Javascript ES6, Django/Django REST Framework, and WordPress & Elementor. Moreover, I have specialized 1+ year of experience in Vulnerability Assessment & Management, Penetration Testing, Reconnaissance, Open-source Intelligence, System & Application Auditing, and Red Teaming Operations. Apart from that, I'm seeking a suitable cybersecurity master's degree abroad where I could reinforce my knowledge and skills to contribute in the research & development of Cyber Security.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Svelte / SvelteKit Frontend Developer | Freelance | Contracts

Several worldwide different employer's on Upwork & Fiverr [01/2020 - Current]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Working experience in Svelte / SvelteKit Development, Django/Django REST Framework Development, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Landing page, Website & Web Application Development, and Web Designing.

Frontend Developer | Full Time

Yoan Systems [10/2019 - 07/2022]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Working experience in Svelte / SvelteKit Development with SSR, Tailwind CSS, KitQL (GraphQL Client), Django REST Framework, Javascript ES6, Typescript, and Bootstrap, Landing page, Web Application Development, and Web Designing.

Security Analyst | Internship

Bytesuit LLC [07/2021 - 02/2022]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Penetration Tester & Cyber Operations Training | Apprenticeship

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [07/2020 - 09/2021]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Conduct penetration testing on several Live VM Cloud Network Environments, Websites & Web Applications, and then Report on Findings. Including Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.



EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Hons.)

National College of Business Administration & Economics (NCBA&E) [15/03/2015 - 30/08/2019]

Address: 31-A Model Town A, Sarwar Shaheed Road, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

Website: https://ncbae.edu.pk/
Field(s) of study: Computer Science

Final grade: CGPA: 3.5/4.0

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Urdu

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Full Stack Development (Svelte / SvelteKit)

Javascipt / Typesript / Python / HTML & CSS / SvelteKit / Django / Object Oriented Programming (OOP) / Django REST Framework / Python Web Automation / Web Scraping / Bootstrap 5 / Svelte Js / Tailwind CSS / Wordpress + Elementor / Javascript (ES6) / Git / JavaScript

Information Security

Penetration Testing / Vulnerability Assessment / Linux (terminal commands, Bash/Shell) / Information Security / WPScan / SQLMap / Open Source Intelligence (OSINT) / Penetration Test (Kali tools, Nessus, CVE) / Metasploit Framework / OWASP Top 10 / Burp Suite / Web Application Security Testing / Nessus / Kali Linux / Nmap

General IT Skills

Microsoft Office / Linux / Windows / Google Office

PROJECTS

Codecrow Landing Page

[08/12/2022 - 16/12/2022]

Codecrow Landing Page built with Sveltekit, Tailwind CSS, Javascript, and Typescript. Include Responsive Web Design

Link: https://github.com/aqeelchishti/cro-website-sv/tree/dev

Fantasy Battle Royale Gaming Website Frontend

[04/2022 - 04/2022]

Fantasy Battle Royale Gaming Frontend Website built with Sveltekit, Tailwind CSS, Javascript, and Typescript. Include Responsive Website Design & Branding

Link: https://github.com/ageelchishti/mvp-web-client

Saleor Sveltekit Ecommerce Web Application

[03/2022 - 04/2022]

Saleor Ecommerce with Sveltekit Frontend Web Application built with Sveltekit with SSR, Tailwind CSS, Javascript, Typescript, and KitQL(GraphQL Client). Include Responsive Web Application Design & Branding



Link: https://github.com/aqeelchishti/saleor-sveltekit-storefront

Bytesuit LLC

[09/2021 - 10/2021]

Information Technology Company Website built with WordPress & Elementor

Link: https://bytesuit.com/

Penetration Testing & Red Teaming Operations Report

[05/2021 - 06/2021]

Working experience in custom VM cloud network environment build testing and live web application [learnaboutsecurity.com] Vulnerability Assessment, Penetration Testing & Red Teaming Operations Report.

Link: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1UnqtlKlbP6CpHX4bYj8lq39i0U2jZAG0aRj0bKogWrA/

Vulnerability Assessment & Penetration Testing Report

[06/2021 - 07/2021]

Working experience in Live VM cloud network environment testing includes Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.

Link: https://docs.google.com/document/d/157vRs9wl_zlD5tAqvXlZ9sMEnscbZbr5i-xuZqlBsAM/

HONOURS AND AWARDS

Ethical Hacker Nanodegree

Udacity [28/06/2021]

Link: https://confirm.udacity.com/TLEEUM7L

Penetration Testing, Network Defense & Cyber Operations

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [09/2021]

Links: https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/pentest-pdf.png | https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/

network_defence-pdf.png

Technical Support Fundamentals

Coursera [12/09/2020]

Link: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/9P9ZNB3RYQQ9

The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Coursera [29/09/2020]

Link: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/V4XW2JFTUNAP

Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User

Coursera [16/10/2020]

Link: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/6QP35BAMRN3P

Crash Course on Python

Coursera [24/12/2020]

Link: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/FPRTQQF3KVSM

Linux Command Line professional

Codecademy Pro [04/09/2020]

Link: https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/Codecademy bash scripting certificate-aqeel-chishti.pdf



Python for Security Professional

Cybrary [09/01/2020]

Link: https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/cybrary-cert-python-for-security-professionals.pdf

Certificate of Proficiency in Information Systems Management (CPISM)

Aptech Computer Education [09/02/2015]

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Working on Pentesting Training Platforms

I really like to work with Penetration Testing training platforms and learn with real-world scenarios. I have already joined platforms like Hack The Box and Try Hack Me.

Gaming

I also like to play Sniper Shooter games. Something like Sniper Ghost Warrior and Sniper Elite series

Playing Badminton

I'm also a badminton player and I took part in several tournaments on the community level in my local area.

Designing Websites and Web Automation

During my studies, I have done several Web Design and Automation projects.